<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-12-13T00:30:28+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Blog Home</title><subtitle>This is my personal site where I put my blogs related to topics such as travel, programming and wildlife.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">A Trip to the Town</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/12/11/trip-to-town.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Trip to the Town" /><published>2017-12-11T12:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-12-11T12:20:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/12/11/trip-to-town</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/12/11/trip-to-town.html">&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, we made a long pending trip to the “town”. It is an area in South Mumbai that is quite distinguished from other parts of the city because of its vintage architecture, cleanliness and the richness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, the “Gang of Four”, that includes me, my better half, my sister and her better half, started it’s trip by visiting the “Hanging Garden” first that is perched on top of a small hillock. It is a nice garden from where you can have a view to the Arabian Sea. Other than that, there is not much to do here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, we reached the Marine Drive. It’s a place that is photographed a lot and you can also find it in almost every bollywood movie that has it’s setting in Mumbai. The place where we sat was opposite to “NCPA” and since I had not seen any play there, my next trip to the town was always finalized. We clicked a huge number of selfies there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time we finished, everyone was quite hungry and so we decided to satiate ourselves. The restaurant that we visited was named “Jimmy Boy” and it was operating as if we were still in the ’70s. The food was great. The “berry pulao” was “berry” good :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the meal was over, we headed to the “Tarapore Aquarium”. Since we reached a little late, the ticket queue had got really long. We could not find an online booking option either. So, it was time to move ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, we reached the “Girgaon Chowpatti”. Everyone went berserk there. We simply devoured the food stalls there. The list included pao bhaji, golgappe, dahi puri, masala chai and the Mumbai’s very own kala khatta. Our group was so busy eating that nobody, except me, went to the beach. By now, it was 6 pm and the traffic was increasing every minute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was time to head back to our respective homes. I had not booked a “Kaali-Peeli” taxi in Mumbai till now. Contrary to the common perception, it is not as expensive. Infact, at the time of booking one such cab, it was cheaper compared to an Ola. The cruise through the sea-link section of the journey was amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a trip went remembering!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Yesterday, we made a long pending trip to the “town”. It is an area in South Mumbai that is quite distinguished from other parts of the city because of its vintage architecture, cleanliness and the richness.</summary></entry></feed>